That is where Tesla bottomed. So, when
you think about how Tesla played out,
the low that was formed in July
corresponded to the S&P putting in a
low,
and the low for the S&P was a lower low
compared to February.
Look at how and I know the nuances are
are, you know, somewhat tricky, but
the
the low in in the early part of the year
the year, January, February, we took out
that low
in the S&P in late June, early July. And
when we took out that low, that is where
Tesla bottomed. And Tesla never went
below that low ever again.
But one of the reasons it never went
below that low ever again is because
when you look at the S&P,
the S&P also actually never went below
that low.
And that's been 16 years ago.